(Gablehauser:)Dr. Koothrappali, have you ever had lunch
in the president's dining room?
(Raj:)I didn't even know
there was a president's dining room.
(Gablehauser:)It's the same food as the cafeteria,
only fresh.
(Gablehauser:)- Come on, little buddy.
- Okay, big buddy.
(Raj:)See you tonight, guys.
- You can stop smiling now.
- Ah.
(Raj:)So anyway, after a fantastic lunch...
(Raj:)...I was whisked off
to the People magazine photo shoot...
- Have any of you been to a photo shoot?
HOWARD: No.
(Raj:)It's fantastic.
(Raj:)Apparently, the camera loves me,
and I it.
(Raj:)They shot me in front of a starry
background where I posed like this:
(Raj:)They're going to digitally add
a supernova.
(Raj:)They say it's the perfect metaphor
for my incandescent talent.
(Sheldon:)Right, a ball of hot, flaming gas
that collapses upon itself.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]